This is Jiuri Mountain.
It's an important place on the Maritime Silk Road.
Mr. Zhao, you came at the right time.
Later,
there will be a wind-praying ceremony here.
I can take some photos for you as a souvenir.
No need.
What wind-praying ceremony?
Mr. Zhao, this...
This way, please. Watch your step.
Mr. Zhao.
Come.
Come, Mr. Zhao, this way please.
This is Jiuri Mountain.
Mr. Zhao.
What do you mean, Mr. Zhao?
Your zipper isn't even zipped.
Zip it up.
Forget it. It's useless even if you zip it up.
What did you say about praying for wind?
Well...
Mr. Zhao.
In ancient Quanzhou,
trade mainly relied on monsoons.
Officials and civilians all came to Jiuri Mountain to pray for wind,
to bless merchant ships for a safe round trip.
Did I ask you?
Mr. Zhao,
we will go buy you a bottle of water.
Let's go.
Why buy water?
Buying water. We are spoiling him.
Are the trekking poles ready?
Is the lens ready?
Are you done venting?
I know you are angry.
I am angry too.
But this is our job.
Understand?
I am very professional.
Mr. Zhao.
I'm sorry about this.
Feel free to let us know if you have any requests later.
We will do our best to meet them.
Right, where is the water you bought?
The water is up there.
Ah, the water.
There's some just ahead, Mr. Zhao.
You can drink it in a bit.
Right.
There's a convenience store up there.
How exactly did you plan this route?
Does this have anything to do with gourmet food?
Mr. Zhao.
If you feel tired,
maybe you should take a rest.
Sitting or lying down is fine too.
I've been lying down for a year.
You guys lie down.
Well.
Mr. Zhao.
Look at you, sweating all over.
Why don't you give me the bag?
Sister.
You are the sister.
Are you jealous?
Have you been jealous lately?
Who's jealous of him?
You're never serious all day long.
I haven't even said who it is yet.
Fine, I am a bit concerned.
Concerned about what?
Look.
I just... I just can't stand the way
he sucks up to my sister.
Acting as a coolie and a yes-man.
What does he want?
I don't like him having ideas about my sister.
My sister has a house and a car.
What gives him the right?
Does he want success without hard work?
Impossible.
Xinyue, you are really bad at lying.
I do have a tiny bit.
Just a tiny bit?
Just...
a tiny bit.
Since when?
I don't know.
Just assume I fell for his looks.
But...
he feels absolutely nothing for me.
It's not fair.
I'm going to nip this tiny bit
in the bud.
How do you know he feels nothing for you?
Just a feeling.
Perhaps with a different state of mind,
you see things from a different perspective.
What do you mean?
Nothing.
How about this?
They say out of sight, out of mind.
Keep your distance from him.
If he's smart, he'll leave you alone.
And you'll forget this tiny bit.
Sound good?
This matter,
no third person can know about.
Understood.
No fourth person will know.
You're jealous.
Are you crazy?
I know it all.
Because I'm close to your sister,
you're jealous.
No, I'm not.
You glare at me whenever I talk to your sister.
And you deny it?
You've got a sister complex.
You're a pig.
Okay, I'm a pig.
I'll change, all right?
A pig doesn't need to change.
Just stay dumb.
Wait a minute. Why don't you let him rest over there?
Let's take a break here.
Are you trying to exhaust yourself?
None of your business.
Hardship
only flows to those who can bear
it.
It would be great if we could see the night view.
But I'm leaving this afternoon.
Mr. Zhao,
would you like to see the photos I just took of you?
This one looks good.
But what's wrong with the composition?
The composition of this one is nice.
I closed my eyes.
The scenery in this one is good.
This portrait...
what is all this?
Mr. Zhao,
it seems you know a lot about photography.
Just a bit.
With a camera,
you just focus,
press the shutter,
and that's it.
Then why are you being so picky?
Come.
Turn around.
Smile.
Pose.
I'm getting a cramp.
I'm getting a cramp too.
I can't hold it anymore.
Mr. Zhao,
why aren't you taking the picture?
Come on.
What's the rush?
I'm not ready yet.
I want the right feel.
Give me the feel, got it?
If you wait until everything is ready,
you'll never press the shutter.
Well, Mr. Zhao.
Mr. Zhao.
Please don't get worked up.
Yes.
Calm down.
This is it.
This is the answer I've been looking for.
Alright, I'm going back.
Mr. Zhao, we haven't reached the top yet.
No need.
On this trip,
I have found the answer I wanted.
Mr. Zhao, wait a moment.
Take it.
Mr. Zhao,
this is Shiting green tea.
I originally wanted to brew it for you
with spring water after reaching the top.
I brought a tea set for you.
This is the last stop of your food tour.
All right.
Actually, on this trip,
you've done a pretty good job.
Mr. Zhao,
let me walk you down.
Don't I have legs?
You two
are quite a good match.
Treat her well.
Yours.
I was shopping at a store recently,
and they were having a lucky draw.
So I happened to win this.
This order is finally completed.
We need to do a proper review later.
Li Xinyue.
Is there a misunderstanding
between us?
This.
Print this out and send it to him.
It counts as a night view.
Our after-sales service is pretty good, right?
It's good.
If you have any work-related questions,
you can ask me.
No need.
It's really pretty.
It sure is.